George Brata

Web Developer





Summary

Versatile web developer with broad experience using various javascript libraries and frameworks, but currently my favorite stack is **Vue.js** / **Nuxt.js** and **Node.js**. I am passionate about the web, digital education and inclusive technologies that make the world a better place for all humanity.

Experience

Senior Developer, Endava

Nov 2022 - Present

Working closely with large software development teams on implementing, testing and delivering web applications for an European corporate client in the real-estate industry.

lan 2021 - Mar 2022

Senior Vue.js Developer, SHE Information Technology

My responsibilities were maintaining a web platform based on FirstSpirit CMS, creating new Vue.js components with Bootstrap and providing support for multilingual content teams.

Jul 2018 - Dec 2019

Frontend Web Developer, **QCatalyst**

Building, testing, deploying and maintaining responsive consumer-facing web applications for National Geographic using modern technologies like React, Redux, Tailwind, Webpack, Storybook, Cypress and Docker.

Ul Developer, 3Pillar Global

Apr 2017 - Apr 2018

Developed financial education learning modules for a US-based client in a React.js app. As a team, we worked with tools like Github, Docker, CircleCl, JIRA, Browserstack and Confluence to deliver high-quality readable code and documentation.

lan 2016 - Apr 2017

Web Developer, Yonder

Migrated a legacy Microsoft Silverlight app to the web with Python and Flask and built the frontend completely from scratch using AngularJS and BulmaCSS.

Feb 2016 - Jul 2022

Trainer, Digital Kids Cluj-Napoca

In my spare time I teach children the computer skills they need to thrive in the 21st century, including the basics of programming, photo/video editing, robotics, web development and other digital abilities.

Education

2014 - 2015 2010 - 2014 Computer Science, *Babes-Bolyai University*, Cluj-Napoca Mathematics - Informatics, *Emanuil Gojdu* High School, Oradea

Why hire me?

Results-driven and people-oriented, I am feeling most comfortable in agile development environments with flat hierarchies and a focus on personal growth. My life-long passion is the Internet and I love ideating and crafting modern, intuitive UX for web applications that solve real-world problems. Beside my regular job as a web developer, over the last 8 years I have successfully delivered multiple <u>freelancing projects</u> using a wide array of tools and technologies for the web and I have participated in more than a <u>dozen hackathons</u> to train exactly those muscles.